Contact

chirag@chiragnayyar.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chiragnayyar (LinkedIn)

www.dconcloud.com (Blog) www.youtube.com/ datacenteroncloud (Personal) mvp.alibabacloud.com/mvp/detail/ more (Other)

Top Skills

Cloud Computing
DNS
Microsoft Technologies

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Punjabi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Microsoft Certified: Azure Administrator Associate AWS Certified Big Data - Specialty

AWS Certified Developer - Associate

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Foundations 2020 Associate

Google Cloud Certified Associate Cloud Engineer

Honors-Awards

Alibaba Cloud MVP

Salesman of the Year 2018-2019

Chirag Nayyar

Cloud Presales

Singapore

Summary

Don't aim for success if you want it; just do what you love and believe in, and it will come naturally. ~David Frost

I am a experienced executive holding Amazon Web Services, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, Oracle Cloud Infrastructure & Alibaba Cloud Certification with a Technical background, effectively delivering integrated IT solutions and Cloud consultancy, along with a genuine passion for Technology, Communications, and Sales.

I started my career with more than 3 years of experience as a Sales Professional and possesses Lead generation attribute, due diligence to qualify lead, systems analysis, marketing and auxiliary operations skills that one is looking for in a candidate. As a true all-rounder, I'm able to carry out assigned projects and tasks in a timely, diligent, and professional manner.

As a Techno Hobbyist, I speak at various Cloud Events and Meetups to share my learning and deriving the path to adopt cloud for all.

I have also contributed in reviewing 5 books on Cloud Platforms by Packt Publishing.

Shoot me a mail if you need to talk to me on any cloud topic. Happy to connect.

chirag@chiragnayyar.com

Experience

Cloud Kinetics 3 years 10 months

Cloud Technical Sales Manager

November 2019 - Present (10 months)

Singapore

Cloud Kinetics is an AWS Premier Consulting partners, Microsoft Azure Gold Partner, Google Cloud Partner and Managed Services partner providing Cloud Consulting, Cloud migration, Product development, DevOps.

I am playing a Techno-Commercial role which is helping CK to grow faster, contributing to Enterprises to start their cloud journey ranging from FMCG, Manufacturing, Media, Finance, E-commerce.

My day to day role is to

- --Work with Technical Account Manager from CK & OEM to make clients successful.
- --Review the pillars of Well Architect Framework.
- --Contributing to implement Cloud Adoption Framework and Security Benchmarks.
- --Setting new Business and digging the existing accounts.
- --Driving the Technical Discussion's which is important to fill the gap between client and CK Solutions Team.
- --Explaining the benefits of Content Delivery Network. especially Cloudfront to improve web app performance and security.

Cloud Sales Lead November 2016 - November 2019 (3 years 1 month) India

CloudKinetics is an AWS Premier Consulting partners and Managed Services partner providing Cloud Consulting, Cloud migration, Product development, DevOps.

I am playing a Techno-Commercial role which is helping CK to grow faster, contributing to Enterprises to start their cloud journey ranging from FMCG, Manufacturing, Media, Finance, E-commerce.

My day to day role is to

--Work with Technical Account Manager from CK & OEM to make my clients successful.

- --Review the pillars of Well Architect Framework.
- ---Contributing to implement Cloud Adoption Framework and Security Benchmarks.
- --Setting new Business and digging the existing accounts.
- --Driving the Technical Discussion's which is important to fill the gap between client and CK Solutions Team.
- --Explaining the benefits of Content Delivery Network. especially Cloudfront to improve web app performance and security.

Education

Punjab Technical University
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science